I love it so much I love it so much I hate it so much I love it so much
I can't help it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it
Today's number one! Good morning.
The staff told me a lot that I am too cute.
Very kind. I am very happy.
When I am told I am cute, I still want to work harder.
I want to become even cuter.
Today, in this one day, I will try my best to become 100 times cuter from my current cuteness.
Today is the music video for the Minato Shoji Laundromat version.
My sister also watches Minato Shoji Laundromat and loves it.
I said, "What's up with GET just playing forever?
She said, "No, I like Minato Shoji Laundromat.
They listen to GET in their rooms and sing along.
They are singing along.
I'm so happy and excited that many Minashow fans will be able to hear this song as well.
I am very happy and excited.
I've seen this on TikTok at the Minato Shoji Laundromat, so I've seen GET dancing.
I've seen Tapia-san and others dancing and stuff like that here, so I'm
I'm happy to be here on location. I'll do my best.
I had a Famichiki, a chocolate pie, and some kind of potato gummies in the morning.
The Famichiki was my mother's request and it was delicious.
It's so cute. It's the outfit they're showing on this tour.
Lots of flowers.
The set for the tour was pretty much a toy set, so I wondered if the costumes would be like that.
I thought the costumes would be like that, too.
But when I saw these flowery outfits
I thought, "Oh, they're coming that way.
But when I heard that they were going to use them for the music video for "KAWAIKO NO KAWAIKO MEMORIAL," I understood.
I understood.
I will let many people see this cute outfit in the music video.
I'll do my best to get it shot as soon as possible.
It's a rare bottom painted tail.
I smile because my eyes were open, and I can't open my eyes.
Crescent smile
It's open.
It's starting.It started.
It was so hard.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle!
The next preview
It's been a long time since I've done something like this.
And..,
The End
Dice, dice, dice, dice, dice, dice!
I'll never let you go.
What about you?
You don't have to tell me. I know.
I think we got it.
You didn't film it?
You got it?
Oh, good, I got it.
Take it if you didn't take it.
I love you so much, sometimes I get a little bit mad.
Don't be a pain. Just take it.
Oh, you're so cute.
The camera's in the washing machine.
Press the button and it spins.
How's it look?
Well, it's kind of fish-eye, so it might be stretched.
Try to keep it centered.
Welcome to the home of the little chicks.
The home of the little chicks, where the little girls can sing.
Don't tell me you're not going to shoot in a laundromat one day?
It's true.
Port girl laundromat!
How do you say Laundromat in Indonesian?
Minato...
harbor three years old marriage setkuso 2
harbor girl laundromat 2
Sparkling... oh, it will reach you.
Good night.Good night.
Club members.
Yankee-chan isn't here?
They're about to start the theater.
How many people in the theater?
Hiyori Forest Theater
Hiyorin Theatre
We'll open anytime.
You're welcome to join us.
Oh, really?
Yes, you're right. You have a cute mouth.
Mr. Suzuki.
Please go out with me.
Yes!
If you win!
I made a mistake! I made a mistake!
So please support us!
Welcome!
If we win
The Cap!
Me!
Please wear it!
Pee!
Put it on!
It's hot out there, folks.
I love you. I'll never let you go.
It's so nice to be cool.
I didn't get any abs.
I have some ground.
Why can't you squeeze me more properly today before bedtime?
That's it.
The "satsutte" part is kinda nice.
You're right.
Where is this place?
Sorry.I'm sorry.
I want to love you, but I hate you.
I don't even have makeup.
I'm just hoping.
I'll never let you go.
Oh, my nose.
Oh, nose.
Oh!
Youth.
I was adolescent.
Cute, cute.
Aww.
Cute. Cute.
Cute, cute, cute. I love it.
Cute, cute, cute. I can't stop. Love, love, love.
We are here at Koi Land, Kangjo City.
We're shooting a promotional video.
Amazing. We shot it in an interesting way.
Looking forward to it?
I'm looking forward to it.
It's not often that I get to go to Dick-in-Land to shoot.
I don't get a chance to go there very often.
And when I saw Minato Seiji, I thought, "Oh, this is that place.
It must be a place that cheers you up.
I am looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
I hate it because I see it in you. I can't stop loving you.
I hate you, I hate you, I hate you.
Because it's a lie. I love you, I love you, I love you.
I love you.
It would have been cute if she had said "I love you.
I mean, she didn't say "I love you".
I see.
It's cute.
I love it.I love you.
If I say I love you, that's the goal, isn't it?
That's for sure.
I'll go around.
Thanks for watching.
Now I won't get my bugs.
I saw a big one just now.
There was a gaga.
Ready go go go.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
It's worthwhile because they laugh at you
Gaga, there was a gaga.
I can't help it, we're in the middle of nature.
That's what you wanted to see.
Even his sleeping habits.
He's so cute.
Even with a grain of rice on it.
It's cute.
Where are you going today?
When are you coming back?
She's so cute, I'm worried.
Have a nice day. See you soon.
Handy Fan. I really need a handy fan this summer.
I think I'll buy one.
It would be nice if I could get some kind of fan out of my cell phone.
The wind blows like a whirlwind.
Let's develop it.
Toki-chan's goods.
Oh, how about a handheld fan?
You can wear it during live performances.
She wears a microphone during MC.
Let's put it on the microphone.
Let's put it on the microphone.Let's put it on the microphone.
How's it look? I don't know.
Ooh!
I love you so much. I hate you so much.
I love it so much, I can't help it.
I love, I love, I love, I love
I love you so much I love you so much
I love you so much I love you so muchEvery day is a sparkle
I can't stop the love, love, love
I hate, hate, hate, hate
I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate, I hate
I love, I love, I love, I love
I'll never let go
What about you?
You don't have to tell me. I know.
Yeah!
Here you go!
Thank you!
Do you have two for the price of one in rock-paper-scissors-paper?
Yes!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh, no, I already bought it...
I already bought it.
I'm already buying!
It's for me!
Oh, hey!
I think I'll have some water.
Water!
I can't drink soda.
It's been too long.
How do you do it?
Hands first.
I'll open it first.
Open it!
You press the "bong" button.
And bam!
Do you want to open it?
I'll go with you then.
I'm not going with you.
I've got a hard-on for this.
Breasts?Breasts.
Sei-no
Oh, ouch, ouch, ouch
Ah, ah, ah, eh, ku, ku, ku, ku, ku, ku, ku...
Yah!
It's the weather!
It's summer!
Summer!
Here we go! Let's go!
You're gonna get so fat!
Like this!
It's good for your costume!
Hard!
They are hard sometimes, aren't they?
Good luck!
Let's put it down!
Yeah!
Oh! There it is!
We've got summer! Cheers!
Yes! Here come the soap bubbles!
Summer!
Cold!
Delicious!
Sounds good!
It just makes me happy!
Peace! Peaceful!
Cute!
Cute.
It's hard.
Thank you.
Aki-chan is really good at taking pictures,
I asked her to take a picture of me when I was wearing my birthday outfit.
It's my lock screen now.Now that's my lock screen.
Orikone.
Lip scene between the two of us.
Since when we liked each other? Lip scene between two people.
You took a favorite scene, right?
I filmed it with Hitori for "I love you".
I love you so much. I love you so much.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I can't stop loving you.
Thank you
Yes, thank you very much
We're done.
It's over.
Good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck
Let's all do our best to get the shot.
Fight!
Why don't you give me more squeezes today before the vacations?
Why didn't you squeeze me more properly?
I don't know anymore.
What a rescue!
Yes, so now
We just finished shooting the promotional video for Cute Memorial.
It was a day full of cuteness!
The first time we shot the video, we were in a laundromat.
The scene where they put the camera in the washing machine and looked into the machine was so cute!
I was so happy to be able to shoot with my favorite swintail today!
Everyone was so cute!
Please take a look at Mr. Tako!
My favorite part was when they put the camera in the washing machine.
I think it's a cute angle of view when the camera is inside the washing machine and everyone is peeking at it like "wow!
I think it's interesting, so I want you to see a lot of it.
The chorus is cute, so I'd be happy if you could imitate it and dance along with me.
It was fun!
I think the music video has a fresh feel to it.
I don't think I've ever had the experience of actually coming to a location like this to shoot a music video.I don't think I've ever had the experience of actually coming to a location like this to shoot a music video, so I'm really looking forward to the finished product.
I'm really looking forward to the completion!
The highlight of the video is that there are two-shot lip shots.
The promotional video is really too cute to be true, so please watch it and be as cute as you can.
I hope everyone will watch it and make it as cute as possible!
We just finished shooting the promotional video for the Gennaga Shoji Laundromat version of "Cute Memorial"!
We actually visited the set used in the drama and went to the filming location.
Since we were able to shoot the video there, it has a different atmosphere than usual.
I think this promotional video may have a lot of things that you know about the atmosphere of this place.
What do you want people to pay attention to?
Well, I think that most of the music videos are in colorful places.
But there are places like a laundromat, a Japanese-style room, or sitting on the porch.
Or sitting on the porch.
I think the place where we are is the highlight of the music video.
I hope you enjoy watching the fusion of cute costumes and Japanese harmony.
I hope you enjoy watching the show.
Please look at it a lot!
Yes, I tried on these cute costumes for the photo shoot.
We also went to the location of the Minato Shoji Laundromat.
We actually filmed at the laundromat.
So please take a look at it.
Please take a look at the drama and the location of the drama.
I hope you all enjoy it!
We've been filming all day today.
For the first time, we were filming right in front of the laundromat.
We are going to sing the theme song for "Minato Shoji Laundromat 2", so we had to go to the location where the song will appear in the drama.
I was very happy to be able to go to the location where the song appears in the drama.
There was a picture taken from inside the laundromat.
Also, we danced outside in front of a house here in this place.
I thought I was able to capture a picture that felt like summer.
I thought I was able to create a picture that would make everyone say how cute I was this summer.
It was a lot of fun!
Thank you for your hard work today.
I hope you all think it's cute and enjoy watching it!
Bye bye!
When I smile, it's as if the world is shining.When I smile, it's as if the world is shining
I can turn the umbrella around and take it easy, because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying And somewhere I'll get wet again
I wonder if it's cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know what's in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart
Paint a piece of the future
It's leading me to the future
Subtitle: Kyou
I can tell you now
Whenever you are lost, remember the reason why you saw it
So that even if it rains, you can smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good-bye Goodbye, Yesterday's Me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a rainbow, rainbow pools, rainbow pours, rainbow pianos.
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye, I was there yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shining.
My heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow, spilling clouds of tears
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Lalala...
Please subscribe to our channel!